gesa.com 2002-06-05

# Gesa's Privacy Policy

* * *

Gesa Credit Union values the relationship that we have with our members and are committed to protecting our members' privacy. We recognize that your trust in us is of central importance, and because of this, the personal information that you provide to us is kept in the strictest of confidence. Gesa has no intention to sell or trade any nonpublic personal information about our members to any third party.

The following privacy policy explains how we use and protect the information about our members. We ask that you read it carefully.

* * *

**NOTICE OF YOUR FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS**

This is our privacy notice for our members. When we use the words "you" and "your" we mean the following types of members:

  * All of our consumer members who have a continuing relationship with us, such as:
  * Deposit account
  * Loan account
  * Credit card
  * Safe deposit box
  * Financial, investment, or economic advisory services (for a fee)
  * Home mortgage brokerage
  * All IRA accounts for which we act as custodian

We will tell you the sources for nonpublic personal information we collect on our members. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information.

We first define some terms.

    _**We**_ , _**our**_ , and _ **us**_ means Gesa Credit Union.
    _**Nonpublic personal information**_ means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records.
    An _**affiliate**_ is a company we own or control.
    A _**nonaffiliated third party**_ is a company that is not an affiliate of ours.

* * *

**THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us
  * Information about your transactions with nonaffiliated third parties
  * Information from a consumer reporting agency

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone, except as permitted by law.

* * *

**THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY AND INTEGRITY  
OF YOUR NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

* * *

**NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION  
AND NONAFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES**

Since we value our member relationship with you, we will not disclose your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. For example, in order to provide members with information about additional products or services, the credit union may disclose information to other financial service providers with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

* * *

**NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION  
AND FORMER MEMBERS**

We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about former members, except as permitted by law.

* * *

**PRIVACY POLICY INQUIRIES**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, contact us by calling (509) 946-1611 or (888) 946-4372, sending us an e-mail at [gesa@gesa.com](mailto:gesa@gesa.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy), or writing to us at Gesa Credit Union, 825 Goethals Drive, Richland, Washington 99352.
